and today is the seventy-four
I won this shirt
da barbearia los salvas
thank you brother
Post Juninho
recognized you
but where did she see you
Juninho was recognized
I returned the coffee
even forgiveness
it was without wanting to
we're going to go into gear before leaving
little time left
actually
we have great possibilities to ride
something
and now i need to do a market research
to really see how much it will cost
for me to invest in my idea
thank you
Right Now
I can't talk much about my business idea
but the idea I want to make
she is a little more expensive than i imagined
trying to figure this out
let's go answer our questions
her price isn't paying more
because it's a problem
it's not a problem nor do you want to pay
become more expensive
that one is not worth it no
if i can't
no dog
cat hunting you will see the same
took a while
until tomorrow
tamo together
come together